<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tiaradwptr</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tiaradwptr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating Office Playbook: Revisiting Self-Management Skills</title>
      <link>/updating-office-playbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updating-office-playbook/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the second month of working from home initiative. My takeaway is: &amp;ldquo;It is mentally draining and hard to keep yourself motivated&amp;rdquo;. Some people have this as their regular routine, but most people, myself included, are required to develop a new set of self-management skills to keep our productivity in check. Here are some of the main topic that I get to identify by this experience:
1. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep track of the priorities Required skill: Better personal timetable design All information seems to come spontaneously due to the sense of &amp;ldquo;flexibility&amp;rdquo; in the working hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Transmission</title>
      <link>/covid-19-transmission/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/covid-19-transmission/</guid>
      <description>PrefaceThis content is created for educational purposes, shout out to louislugas from GitHub for the content inspiration. Check out his awesome web application for COVID-19 transmission network analysis. This article will focus on breaking down building blocks in creating network analysis taking on the most recent COVID-19 pandemic outbreak in Indonesia. There are exponentially rising amount of suspects and patients on this matter and a strategic approach in containing the spread will be required in decision makings in this country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi.</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>You seems to have discovered my site The time I&amp;rsquo;m writing this, the website is not planned to be publicly announced. This is my first trial in publishing a personal website. I am currently teaching data science and building stuff at Algoritma. I enjoy fiddling with data and codes (a bit of coding with a lot of praying and googling). The handsome avatar in the top left you are looking right now is Bolin, my cat, please shower him with lots of love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interesting Title Not Found</title>
      <link>/interesting-title-not-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/interesting-title-not-found/</guid>
      <description>Yup, this post has no other purpose than to just sit here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>